JuanRodriguez

A Front End Developer with an expertise in modern HTML - CSS - Javascript across various frameworks, extensive insight on user interaction, web layouts, responsive design and working knowledge of database structure in order to consume RESTful APIs.

Experience

March 2017 - Current



MediaScience Labs

Front End Developer

- Manage Media Science's user facing projects
- Maintain panelist site by updating and pushing improvements on a daily basis
- Created a central panelist dashboard that allows users to: submit surveys,
 update profile information, enter into a points/rewards system
- · Created a texting module for direct access to users using twilio api
- Partner with marketing team to implement online campaign initiatives
- Troubleshoot potential programming issues at on-site studies

March 2016 - Sept 2017



DCR Point-of-Sales Systems

Associate Developer

- Implemented user friendly features for the in-house data monitoring system
- · Created a department specific website to showcase new projects
- · Refactored existing code to reduce the risk of error
- Installed OTA updates to stores around the country

Education

July 2015 - Dec 2015



Nashville Software School

Web Developer

- A six-month, full-time software boot camp for problem-solving web development
- Created individual and collaborative single page applications
- Implemented MVC design patterns
- Utilized Git in a team environment

August 2006 - Dec 2010



Texas State University

B.A. in Theatre

Community

July 2015 - Dec 2015



Technology Director

The Austin Gay and Lesbian Pride Foundation

Skills



HTML CSS Javascript SASS ES6 Vue.js Angular 1.5
Node.js Firebase Git Webpack Sketch Responsive Design